# MAHESH KUNWAR

Sydney, NSW 2042 | 0426182792 | kunwarmahesh29@gmail.com

# Summary

Hardworking employee with customer service, multitasking and time management abilities. Devoted to giving every customer a positive and memorable experience. Highly-motivated employee with desire to take on new challenges. Strong worth ethic, adaptability and exceptional interpersonal skills. Adept at working effectively unsupervised and quickly mastering new skills.

#### Skills

- Fluent in English
- Flexible and Adaptable
- Leadership Customer Service
- Active Listening Networking
- Organizational Skills
- Calm Under Pressure
- Friendly, Positive Attitude

### Experience

#### Ccok

pizzza boccone - Sydney, NSW

- Mar 2022 to Current
- Prepared meals according to recipes and menus, adjusted ingredients and cooking times accordingly.
- · Cleaned kitchen equipment, surfaces, utensils and dishes.
- Adhered to food safety standards when storing and preparing foods.
- · Ordered supplies as needed for the kitchen.
- · Checked quality of ingredients before use in order to ensure freshness.
- · Maintained a clean working environment by sweeping, mopping floors, washing surfaces and emptying trash cans.
- Tasted all prepared dishes in order to check flavorings, texture and presentation prior to serving them to customers. Provided guidance to junior cooks regarding food preparation methods and
- techniques.

#### Kitchen Hand

Sep 2022 to May 2023

- metisse Potts Point, Nsw
  - · Cleaned dishes, pots, pans and utensils.
  - Swept and mopped floors to maintain cleanliness in the kitchen area.
  - Set up serving travs for events or parties.
  - · Checked temperatures of freezers, refrigerators and hot holding units regularly to
  - ensure food safety standards were met. · Served food during catered events or banquets as requested by supervisors or chefs.
  - · Operated dishwashers to sanitize dishes and silverware.
  - · Maintained a neat work station throughout shift hours.
  - · Restocked condiments on tables throughout restaurant dining room. Inspected kitchen equipment for proper functioning before use.
  - Maintained inventory of kitchen supplies and equipment needs.
  - · Kept records of food waste to track usage levels.
  - · Cleaned and sterilized dishes, countertops and utensils to prevent bacteria growth.
  - · Peeled and cut fruit and vegetables to prepare for cooking or serving.
  - · Acquired new skills to support team and further accommodate customer needs.
    - Transported trash to dumpster, properly disposing of expired food items.
  - · Prevented spoilage or cross-contamination by storing food in designated containers and areas.

#### Kithen Hand

manta restaurant - Wolloomooloo, Nsw

- · Cleaned dishes, pots, pans and utensils.
- Swept and mopped floors to maintain cleanliness in the kitchen area.
- · Stocked shelves with food supplies, such as canned goods and dry ingredients. Received deliveries of food items and stored them properly.
- Set up serving travs for events or parties.
- Operated dishwashers to sanitize dishes and silverware.
- · Followed all health code guidelines when handling food items.
- · Organized storage areas for efficient access to items when needed.
- · Inspected kitchen equipment for proper functioning before use. Maintained inventory of kitchen supplies and equipment needs.
- Sanitized surfaces with approved cleaning solutions after each task was completed.
- · Communicated effectively with co-workers regarding daily tasks assigned.

## **Education and Training**

Apr 2022 to Aug 2022